No living creature was hurt during
the production of this show.
Please contact us for any inquiries
turkision@gmail.com
Osman!
You have no place to escape!
Son!
Hold on.
Archers!
Alps!
Shields!
Aim!
Brother!
Shoot!
Defend!
Aim!
Shoot!
Hold on! Hold on!
Hold on!
Flatyos!
Alps!
Aim!
Shoot!
Hold on brothers!
- Brother.
- Aim!
- Shoot!
Aim!
Shoot!
- Close up!
- Aim!
Shoot!
Hold on valiants!
Hold on son!
Come on brothers, resist!
My lion, hang on.
Aim!
Forward!
- We must get out of here, brother!
- We will, brother, we will!
- We have to leave here.
- Alps! Hang on!
Hold on.
Hold on my valiants!
Move!
Shields!
Now!
Now! Now!
Now! Close up!
Close up!
Hold on brothers.
We will get out of here!
Come on!
Protect the woundeds!
Come on Alps!
Boran!
Protect me!
Hold on.
Pull the woundeds!
Come on!
- We are going to carry the woundeds!
- Come on son!
Hold on everyone!
- Hold on Bayhoca!
- He can't get up.
Pull the woundeds!
Pull!
- Baysungur!
- My Bey!
Come on!
Pull!
Everyone, move!
Come on!
- Help, Alps!
- Come on son!
Close up!
Ya Allah! Bismillahirrahmanirrahim
"In the name of God, the Most Gracious, the Most Merciful."
Hold on Alps!
Wait.
Where were you?
Where were you uncle?
- I went to Nicola, nephew.
- What did you say?
I said "Do you think I am a betrayer?" to
him so that he doesn't suspect me.
It seems you are in the wrong way
to me, uncle.
Osman must die.
That Osman who take us to one war to
another, who set us against our own people
He must die.
You are worried about Aygül.
You are right.
However, she is going after her own
destiny.
Do not tire yourself up.
Do you think that is easy, Hatun?
She is my beloved daughter.
She doesn't appreciate my fatherhood, but
she is my heart.
I want life for my daughter and
death for Osman...
from my Allah.
I am waiting with my arms folded...
I can't do anything for both of them.
Don't blame yourself, my Bey.
Don't.
Wait. Wait.
You are right, Hatun.
You are right.
We are going to wait.
We will hear Osman's death.
And I am going to be the Bey.
We are going to wait.
Wait!
Now open!
Stab!
Don't stop!
Now open up!
Stab!
Close up!
Open up!
Stab!
Close up!
Hold on valiants!
Open up!
Stab!
Close up!
Hold on!
Alps!
We retreat!
Retreat!
Now!
- Don't let them escape!
- Retreat!
Forward!
This way, my Bey.
Hold on son.
Hold on my lion!
We are close!
Alps, hold on tight!
Come on my lion!
Hold on my valiant!
I'm here!
Hold tight.
Get the other woundeds!
Hold on my valiant!
Hold on!
Hold on son!
Careful here!
Hold on son.
Go!
Easy, easy.
Come on.
Come on Alps.
Come on Alps!
Let's go!
Shields!
Get out of the way, soldier!
Why are you standing? Go forward, soldier!
Don't let them escape.
They keep the passage!
There are archers, we can't get through!
Osman! You can't escape this time!
Soldier, clear the way!
- Passage is open!
- Soldier!
Get out of my way, soldier!
They have archers, we can't get in.
Osman! Damn it!
Nicola, we can't let him run away. He lost
most of his Alps. He can't deal with us now
Let me finish this.
Let Osman suffer from the defeat.
You shall enjoy your victory, Flatyos.
Nicola, I want to serve you wine in Osman's
skull when you come back from Constantine.
My saint friend, Rome was not found in one
day. Do not let your victory be a defeat.
Enjoy the vengeance of your father.
Soldier, bring me fire!
Take the documents from Göktuğ.
Then kill him.
Also find the betrayer in the castle
before I arrive.
Don't worry, Nicola.
Come on soldier, come on!
Come on son.
Brother, we are close.
Come here.
Brother, come on.
This was your first war, and it shall not
be the last, inshallah (if Allah permits).
This wound won't kill you.
I will thank to Allah one thousand times
for fighting with you, my Bey!
Osman Bey, we have been entrapped.
We have been betrayed.
My Bey, Nicola knew we'd come.
The penalty for betrayal is fined
by sword.
Anyone's blood, even my father's,
is Halal, my Bey.
- Alps, bring the horses.
- Okay my Bey.
Brother take Aygül and the woundeds to
the tent.
- I am not going back without Flatyos.
- Let me go with you, brother.
Brother, go with them. If I fail,
we can't find the betrayer.
Be careful.
We passed the dirty paths thanks to
our faith!
We know how to set a trap the best!
Our swords shall break if we can't make
the infidels pay!
We swear on our eyes which have
seen treachery.
Our breaths shall be Haram if we can't
shed their blood!
Our breaths shall be Haram!
(if we can't shed blood)
Osman must have sent the woundeds
on horse.
He must have left by foot.
They are few in number.
But he has the best Alps.
Soldier, we split!
I don't accept any mistakes!
Lena.
I know you are worried about Bayhoca.
Do not be. They will come back
safe and sound inshaallah (if Allah permits.)
How can I not be, Bala?
We couldn't enjoy Bayhoca's birth.
When my deceased son was little...
I lost him.
I went dry, couldn't breastfeed
Bayhoca enough.
We used to go to his brother's grave.
Don't, Lena. Bayhoca went there with
his father and his uncle.
He wanted to be a Ghazi.
Our valiants live for holy wars, don't
you know that?
Bayhoca saw himself in his dream
last night.
A little bird.
Little like himself.
Worried.
An impatient bird.
The bird flew off, he said.
Maybe it's not a life bird.
Maybe it was all his problems
that flew off.
The war he went with his father and uncle
took all of his problems away.
Sword in one hand, bridle in the other.
May Allah bless his fight.
Amin.
May Allah grant us with our loved ones.
I knew what it is like to be a Hatun of
an Alp. I was destined to suffer from...
the pain of being an Alp's mother.
I shall leave.
I have things to do.
Of course.
I witnessed my brothers' deaths.
My mother couldn't resist to all the pain.
I feel her.
This land taught us that fear doesn't
change the end.
My Osman Bey will eventually pay both
Nicola and Flatyos.
So Osman Bey and his Alps went to
finish it, huh?
He won't come back before he finishes
this. I know it.
Don't worry.
I am not worried about two ignobles who
Osman Bey is after.
What I am worried about is what Potter
İdris says before he dies.
- Whose dog are you?
- I'll tell you. I'll tell you.
I'll tell you all. The betrayers are
so close to you, Osman Bey.
What do you mean, Hatun?
Like dog İdris said, Osman Bey should have
avoid the nearest enemy.
He should have found the betrayer
in the tent first.
Even his Alps don't know what they
are fighting for, where they are headed.
Don't worry about Osman Bey.
My Father says the ones who we trust the
most teach us to not trust anyone.
What are you trying to say, Malhun Hatun?
There was no one to know we were going to
battle except for his Beys. Don't you hear?
Should he suspect Savcı Bey, or Dündar Bey
whose daughter is in the war?
Or Gündüz Bey who is ready to
sacrifice his life for his brother.
You are talking nonsense.
Bala Hatun.
You are getting angry, but don't you see
that I am worried about Osman Bey?
Osman Bey has been my hope for my people.
I won't let anything bad hap...
Osman Bey is hope for all of us
Malhun Hatun!
He hasn't lost any war he was in so far!
You can stay cool!
I will neither stay cool nor confirm
this land to my father...
unless I find the owner of the arrow
that shot İdris.
I shall leave.
I need to leave you to your coolness.
Good luck with it.
- Take it, have a nice day.
- May Allah bless you.
I always wondered about the dirt that
will come out when I scalp you.
Geyhatu's hunt dog Böke.
How did you find out Kızıl Bey's son Umur
was after us, Petrus? How did you track us?
How did you inform us?
I am responsible for the flying birds,
the running foxes...
the venomous snakes hereabouts.
Just like I know where Umur Bey is.
Where is he?
If Black Shaman Togay agrees with me...
You are going to find out where he is.
Both Togay and I know very well why
Turks are rushing to west.
I know who has the certificate of occupancy
of Osman and Turkmens.
What do you want in return?
- We have a common enemy with Geyhatu.
- Osman.
I will give Umur Bey's tent to Togay
in return of Osman's head.
No.
Nephew!
No!
Bayhoca!
Hold on Ghazi! I want something from you.
Do not die!
- Bayhoca!
- Brother, what happened?
I'll tell you later, brother.
- No, no, no!
- Easy!
Bayhoca!
No no no!
Lena!
Move!
You can't leave us.
Lena!
Move! Help Alps!
Get the care tent ready immediately!
Take the wounded alps there!
Pull yourself together!
Hold on!
Osman is absent.
Thank Allah, Aygül is back.
- Mother, I will be gone.
- No no!
No you can't leave us!
Let's carry him!
Come on Alps!
Carry the woundeds!
Hold on son!
Hatuns! Let's get the care tent ready!
- Don't shake him!
Get the care tent ready!
- Hold on nephew!
- Clear the way!
I won't leave you Bayhoca!
- I won't leave you Bayhoca!
- Hold on nephew!
What are you waiting for, Dündar Bey.
Go help the woundeds.
Bring clear cloth!
Gonca! Gonca.
Compress the wound with the cloth Gonca.
- Hold on.
- Inshallah.
Bring it at once!
I'll brand the wound!
How did you got ambushed?
They knew that we were coming.
Come on, come on!
His bleeding won't stop, his bleeding
won't stop Savcı!
Open your eyes, please
Don't close your eyes!
Son, hold on, son.
Hold on my valiant! Open your eyes,
don't leave us like that son!
- Baysungur, tell me what happened?
- My Bey, Nicola knew everything.
We got ambushed, they shot Bayhoca.
What happened? Where is the rest?
Where is Osman?
We got ambushed.
We have martyreds.
And woundeds.
Osman Bey went after Flatyos with
a bunch of alps.
I told you! The betrayer is so close! They
know everything about Osman Bey's plan.
Hatun! This not the right time!
Are you going to help or what?
How did you know we were going to
got ambushed, Göktuğ?
Zülfikar.
May God protect our soldiers.
Amen.
May God grant Lord Nicola with victory
on his ambush against Osman.
Amen.
I have to get to Osman Bey.
Zülfikar Dervish ha?
Valiant Zülfikar.
He shall live long.
Now they will be in the middle of the
ambush.
Leave Flatyos to me.
He'll give me the betrayer in the tent.
Wait for my sign.
Alps!
Flatyos.
Do you think I will surrender, Osman Bey?
I knew I'd entrap you like the back of
my hand.
To death, then.
Let's begin.
Go on, finish it Osman Bey.
I told you.
Your won't go easily.
You'll tell me everything until your
tongue goes rotten.
How did Cumans get in our tent?
You get in and out of our castle
constantly, and now this is what you say?
Tell me.
Who did the potter serve to?
Who told you about my plan for Nicola?
Who, ha? Who!
Every community has betrayers inside,
Osman Bey.
He doesn't have the face to come back,
Hatun.
He is trying to convert the defeat
to victory.
He'll die so that he can show everyone
he won and got his revenge.
It was obvious that his greed would
drag him down.
Inshallah he can't come back so that other
Alps can live.
He won't be able to come back, Hatun.
Don't you see his Alps, they are
exhausted. He can't get Flatyos.
He won't be able to come back.
Alps!
Take him to the tent.
I'll make him talk before he breaths
for the last time.
Go.
Brother.
One last duty is waiting for you.
I know my Bey. They'll come to get
the certificate of occupancy.
I'll learn who are the spies of Papa,
who cooperates with Nicola.
If you can succeed, we will find out who
the betrayer is in the tribe.
- May Allah help you.
- Eyvallah(thank you) my Bey
Let's move!
Open your eyes son!
Don't leave us alone!
Father!
Where is my sword?
I'll fetch it son!
No, Bayhoca! Don't leave!
- Son! Son!
- Open your eyes!
Here is your sword son!
Open your eyes!
Give me your blessings.
Don't son! Don't!
Open your eyes!
Hold on my valiant!
Don't leave us Bayhoca!
Being a Ghazi...
- You can't leave!
- Shahada...
You can't leave!
I bear witness that there is no deity
but Allah...
and I bear witness that Muhammad is the
messenger of Allah.
No, no, no, Bayhoca!
Bayhoca open your eyes!
Open your eyes!
No, no!
Bayhoca open your eyes!
Please don't leave us!
Open your eyes!
Open your eyes Bayhoca!
Bayhoca open your eyes!
Please don't leave us alone!
Open your eyes!
Open your eyes Bayhoca!
Open your eyes my son, please!
How can you do it, Savcı?
How can you clothe him?
He is in Jannah, Hatun.
Don't cry anymore.
Why did you take him to the
battle, Savcı?
Why did you?
Oh Bayhoca...
Bayhoca...
The good ones live less, Lena.
Valiants go first.
Bayhoca...
No, no, no!
He deceased with no sin, Lena.
No, no!
He died before the world dirt him.
No, no...
I know this pain the best, my nephew.
There's nothing else to do then
being patient.
There is not.
He was a brave valiant.
He must be in Jannah now.
Bayhoca...
Get up, my child get up...
Please...
What is it, uncle?
Where are you headed?
Osman.
You are back, huh?
We were worried about you.
We got ambushed.
We killed the infidels, inshallah.
I know, I know, Masha Allah (praise be)
And Flatyos...
Bala.
Who is this martyr lying down in
my tent?
I failed, brother, I failed.
I couldn't protect him.
He slipped through my hands.
He's gone.
He flew off like a little bird.
Oh Bayhoca.
Oh, my nephew.
You wanted to be a Ghazi.
You fought in the middle.
But you are a martyr now.
You are a martyr now.
A martyr.
You are in Jannah.
But...
but you burned your uncle's heart.
Help me, brother.
Help me find that dog.
I won't relieve until I kill him.
Brother.
Did you think I'd come here without
that dog?
Do you have him brother?
I do.
- So, you have him.
- I do.
Flatyos is here.
I will kill him.
- Lena.
- I'll kill him! Let go of me!
Lena!
Bala, stay here.
Osman brought Flatyos to make him talk.
If he speaks...
If he speaks, then be ready for anything,
Hatun.
We may need to run away.
Run away?
To where are we going to run away
Dündar Bey?!
If Flatyos speaks...
Don't let someone else kill me, Dündar Bey.
You should kill me.
What are you talking about Hatun? If things
come to that, why would I kill you?
There are a lot of men to kill.
Then kill him.
Or make someone do it.
Here we go again.
For how long do you think you'll keep me.
My Bey already told you, until your
tongue goes rotten.
The previous visit of mine was short.
We'll see if you can run away when
your legs are broken.
Bamsi Bey is here as well.
Of course he wouldn't miss the show.
Flatyos... Flatyos...
Where are you going to go before we make
pay for the Alps and Suleiman Shah's
beloved one Bayhoca.
Is it only Bayhoca, Bamsı Bey?
Remember Dumrul who I riddled with holes,
Ayaz whose stomach I slit.
Do you want me to count more?
My Allah shall witness me, I won't die
before I smell your dead body.
Stop, daughter.
Bamsi Bey.
Let me.
Let me spit on my son's killer's face.
You didn't give me your love, but
you gave your son, Lena.
- Die!
- Stop, aunt.
Stop.
In order not to let more mothers cry...
I must make this dog talk.
Let go.
If you let my son down before he
goes into the grave...
I won't give you my blessings, Osman Bey.
- Tell me what happened.
- We lost Commander Flatyos.
How can it be?
How did this happen?
Göktuğ attacked us with Cumans.
Göktuğ?
I should have seen that!
I should have seen that damn it!
Soldier, inform Constantinople.
Now!
Flatyos!
There are a lot of betrayers in your
tribe, Osman.
Talk.
Talk so you die in the easy way.
I always wanted the hard way, Osman.
To kill your father.
I wanted Lena.
I know the potter is not alone here.
Who is the other betrayer?
Talk!
Who?
Tell me!
Potter's soul came to finish his
uncomplete job, Osman.
Who are Papa's spies?
Who did Nicola ally with?
With whom?!
So many enemies you have, Osman.
Nicola was confused to choose.
You were lucky today, Osman.
But this will not last long.
Nicola will capture you now or later.
Brother.
His yours.
Yours.
Do you know why I aimed for Bayhoca,
Savcı Bey?
Who is the betrayer that told
we were after Nicola.
Because you took my love.
And I took your son.
Beys, I prefer cutting my tongue to speak!
Boran1
Osman Bey! This dog won't speak.
Each breath of his will create chaos.
Kill him.
Uncle! Many Alps' blood is in this
dog's hand.
Don't say it again.
This one won't die until he speaks.
Brother, until his last breathe...
he'll tell us everything he knows.
I am telling you, the betrayer is not far,
they are right near you.
Watch your mouth, Hatun.
Just tell who you are accusing.
You are in pain.
You can't see things.
I'll reveal it.
What are you going to reveal?
Are you here to create chaos, Hatun?
What is your problem?
Bala Hatun, let go of my arm first.
No need to create chaos in this tent.
There's chaos and treachery in every
corner.
Don't you see it?
He can't die...
Why is he still alive?
Why aren't you still keeping him alive,
Savcı?
He'll die, Hatun.
He'll die.
In the most fearful way.
He can't get away with this.
Each breath he takes flare up the
fire in my heart.
Why Osman Bey doesn't want us to take
revenge, kill the murderer of our son?
How can I live with it?
How can my heart bear up?
Do you think I am not in pain, Hatun?
Do you think it was easy to see him dying,
Hatun?
But...
We have to find the betrayer in the tribe.
- We don't have to!
- Lena
- Lena...
- We don't have to, Savcı Bey.
- Lena.
- Kill him.
Savcı Bey ki...
Lena!
Be calm, Hatun.
Keep calm, my Lena.
Keep calm.
- Keep calm.
- Savcı Bey.
Kill him!
Kill!
Don't want him from me, brother.
Don't.
Osman.
Brother...
I can't look at Lena's face.
Come on, Flatyos won't talk.
He will, brother.
He will.
Now or later, I'll make him talk.
It'll take months, brother.
My Hatun is pregnant.
She can't do it while Flatyos is here.
Let me take the revenge of my child.
Brother, your pain is my pain.
Your lament is my lament brother.
He is your son, my nephew.
I know how unbearable this pain is.
However, you should feel me too.
Let me take revenge of my son before
he kills my unborn child too.
Brother, tell my aunt that...
Osman will kill Flatyos in every breath
he takes, slowly.
Killing Flatyos for once is a gift
for him.
Don't break us one more time, Osman.
Let me finish this.
Go, brother.
Go away.
Let's not make our pain stronger.
Go away from my presence before
we fall out with each other.
My valiant father.
You taught me how to be like
a lion in the war and...
how to be calm in peace.
I sacrifice my head in your way, father.
But, show me a way out now.
Show me a way, my Ghazi father.
How hard it is to be a Bey...
in all these treacheries...
in all this pain.
Can I, nephew?
Come uncle.
Osman Bey doesn't let you, does he?
I know how painful losing a child is.
That pain burns your heart.
I know it.
Osman Bey is also right, uncle.
We have to make Flatyus talk to
find out the betrayer.
Do you think he'll talk?
That snake will not talk.
Whoever that ignoble dog betrayed us will
capture him from the tent!
I will choke him!
Of course you will.
You have the right.
You have the right to kill him.
I support you nephew, I support you.
Uncle, let me think.
Let me think.
She comes and goes around,
she provokes me.
What does she say, Hatun?
What does she say?
How does she provoke you?
She says there are betrayers among us
They are so close to us but we don't see.
She is right.
There's a betrayer among us and he is
so close to us.
Is it Malhun Hatun's job to reveal
him, Osman?
We have been betrayed, we should
find him.
No one can involve in our issues
and make us feel small!
My Bala, my heart burns.
My heart burns.
I can barely stand not to kill
that Flatyos.
Do not push me.
Forgive me my Osman.
Until I kill that dog, I am not me.
I am..
not me, Hatun.
Wait for my heart to cool off.
Get out.
My Bey, don't.
Osman Bey has a certain command.
Let Lena Hatun out, my Bey.
- Don't do it please.
- Osman Bey wanted me to make him talk.
Baysungur, get away.
- My Bey, don't.
- Baysungur! Move!
This is the last time I'm asking.
Who is the betrayer?
You'll live with the hole I dig
in your heart forever.
I won't die as long as you die.
In each breath, every time you remember
your son...
You'll remember me.
You won't be able to kill me.
I'll live in your hearts.
Burn in hell, ignoble man.
I will take revenge of my son.
I appreciate you Lena.
You let go of my pain.
This is for my son Bayhoca.
Vengeance...
and a sweet dream.
A dream that I don't want to wake up.
A flavour I won't forget...
the taste of.
Die!
My Bey, what have you done?
Farewell, Lena.
Farewell.
My Bey!
Can I come, my Bey?
Come in.
Tell me, Boran Alp.
What happened?
Flatyos.
What happened to him?
Do you want to see my anger?
I killed him.
- We killed him.
- Lena!
We took our son's revenge.
What did you do?
What did you do, brother?
Brother.
Why didn't you listen to me?
Why?
Every breath he took was a torture to me.
I couldn't resist.
Do whatever you want.
It's not just about Flatyos.
A traitor from my tent...
is involved in the murder of my nephew.
Brother...
Tell me.
What happens now? Brother?
How will we find that traitor?
Every breath he takes will be
torture to us.
Tell me.
Bala!
Lena!
The baby is coming!
Boran Alp. Tell Hatuns to bring warm
water and clean cloth. Come on!
O Gazriin Ezen... (According to Tengrism, the earth is the home of a great variety of spirits, including Gazriin Ezen.)
When the black hawk sings...
When the black shaman brings death...
Black Shaman Togay.
There was more time.
She's early, Osman Bey.
What if something happens to Lena?
What if something happens to my child?
Don't worry.
He's hurrying up to help his father.
Yes.
He's coming to relieve your wounds.
- Inshallah, brother.
- Inshallah.
Thank Allah.
Thank Allah...
Mashallah!
His uncle dies for him.
Bala Hatun...
Don't worry.
It's a boy.
- Mashallah.
Is Lena Hatun okay?
- Thank Allah, she is.
My son.
Look, brother.
I have a son.
You have a nephew.
Congratulations, brother.
Congratulations.
Savcı brother. I should
take him to his mother.
I will come with you.
My Osman Bey...
Allah's miracles are countless.
Allah gives and takes everything.
Kongar, you'll go to forest spirits
that bring death.
Geyhatu never forgives betrayal!
I'll send you to the
hell you have come from, Togay!
For the black storm!
"In the name of Allah, the Most
Gracious, the Most Merciful."
"Never say that those martyred in
the cause of Allah are dead...
...in fact, they are alive...
with their Lord, well provided for
rejoicing in Allah’s bounties
and being delighted for those
yet to join them.
There will be no fear for
them ...
nor will they grieve...
They are joyful.
Allah said, how good and true way.
"Glorified is your Lord—the Lord of Honour and Power—above what they claim!"
Peace be upon...
the messengers...
And praise be to
Allah—Lord of all worlds."
Al-Fatihah.
Dying is to live out.
It is to give your life to its owner.
Martyrs are witnesses.
They pray with their blood
and wait for Allah's news.
Don't call them "the dead."
Because they're alive.
You don't see it.
They are with Allah.
Allah said that.
You don't see.
Bayhoca is alive and he is happy.
He was...
brave...
like his ancestors.
He was manful.
He always wanted to fight.
He chose martyrdom.
He left Kayı tent...
for the Prophet.
May Allah...
forgive his sins.
Amin.
May Allah grant us martyrdom.
Bayhoca.
Look, son.
Your brother is a hero.
He couldn't see you.
He couldn't.
For those who believe, there is
no separation.
He'll see him.
A bird comes...
another bird flies.
I was in a place full of white.
Pure white.
A bird came out of my mouth.
It flew.
It became invisible.
It's like it was flying from
a cage, mother.
It flew.
He'll know what a valiant his brother was.
He'll try to be valiant like him.
Inshallah.
- Peace and prayer be upon
you, o Messenger of Allah. -
We should bury him.
Bismillahirrahmanirrahim. (In the name of Allah, the Most Gracious, the Most Merciful.)
Come on, Lena.
No!
Don't!
No, no.
Don't take him, please!
Bayhoca. No!
- Peace and prayer be upon
you, o Messenger of Allah. -
No! No!
Please don't take him!
Don't take him! Please!
I beg you!
Don't take him!
Don't take him there!
They are all fake.
Togay doesn't like lies.
Let me go, I'll take you to Osman.
He'll take you to Umur Bey.
How?
I have an informer in the tent.
Dündar.
He is Osman's uncle.
Let's go.
My Bayhoca.
Sleep well, my child.
Sleep well, son.
Sleep well.
Son.
My son.
My child.
You left me...
like the sword flowers...
that blossoms when the sun comes.
You left me.
I couldn't get enough of you, son.
I couldn't.
Your soil...
I will water your soil..
with my tears, son.
Don't worry, son.
We took your revenge.
We killed...
the murderer of our life.
Me and your mother...
We took your revenge, son.
We took your revenge.
Rest in peace.
Rest in peace, son.
What will we do without you?
You made big promises in front of me...
and you convinced us that you
were the right person.
When I heard that you
took over Kulucahisar...
I felt that I gave the
duty to the right person.
You gave Kulucahisar back to Osman.
You caused my soldiers to be killed by
Turks.
Osman is planning to occupy İnegöl.
You promised victory!
Is this victory?
Answer me, Nikola.
When you summoned me, I defeated Osman.
I killed his soldiers...
and I won a victory.
- What?
- I have news for Nikola.
Tell us.
Osman got out of the trap.
Flatyos was taken to Kayı tent.
- Is this the victory you talk about?
- Flatyos...
Another incompetent one.
Incompetent?
I give you one last chance, Nikola.
You will work with someone.
Kalanoz's brother.
A valiant member of Kalanozs.
Efaristos Kalanoz.
Go and empower İnegöl.
If you let Osman take İnegöl, you'll die.
Don't forget that.
Act like a soldier, Nikola!
I won't act like a soldier, Emperor.
I will act like a lion...
I'll kill Osman and his loved ones!
We still don't know who the traitor is.
I'll kill him.
It's not the end.
You're right, Osman Bey.
You're right.
Who'd think that the potter is a traitor?
We'll be careful.
We'll suspect everything and everyone.
We'll follow every trace
and every suspicion.
Until we find that traitor.
I gave Göktuğ a duty.
However, there's still no news.
What kind of duty, Osman Bey?
They want documents.
Göktuğ will deceive Helen with these.
Then they will bring Göktuğ to those
who want the documents.
It's a difficult duty.
Difficult.
I hope they won't harm Göktuğ.
You're right.
There's something wrong.
Brother...
Go with the Alps.
Find Göktuğ for me.
Don't worry, Osman Bey.
Your command.
Thank you.
Can I come in, Osman Bey?
Come in.
Tell me, Malhun Hatun.
My father is about to arrive.
He's coming here for your promises.
I want to visit him if you let me.
Good.
I want to see Umur Bey.
We should go together.
My father will come to see you, Osman Bey.
Don't bother.
What do you mean, Malhun Hatun?
I mean that only three of us know that my
father is coming here.
Malhun Hatun believes that the traitor is
someone close to you, Osman Bey.
You...
- want to protect your father.
- His Alps are with him.
However, they are few in number.
They are coming.
I don't want to endanger my father.
No one should know where we are going.
Don't worry.
No one will know.
Your father and your people will come
here safe and sound.
My Alps will ensure safety.
Then I should be prepared.
The Great Osman Bey will
welcome Umur Bey, huh?
I won't welcome a Bey...
I will see the important part of
the army that I will build.
Take care then, Osman Bey.
I hope you return quickly.
Bala Hatun.
Ever since Malhun Hatun came here...
you've been cold towards me.
My Bey.
She looks at everywhere.
She's everywhere, wherever I go.
Bala.
Ever since she came, she has witnessed
many betrayals.
She's right to worry about her tent.
I don't trust anyone
who doesn't trust you.
Have a nice journey.
Can I come in?
Come in.
How could a big army let Osman go?
He was defeated.
Everyone saw his defeat.
- It's a victory for you, Dündar Bey.
- What victory?
He caught Flatyos.
I'm sure he didn't talk.
Savcı handled it.
Our Alps are dead. They were my children.
I feel sorry.
You don't have much time to...
clean the blood on
your hands with Osman's blood.
- Osman will find out sooner or later.
- Don't worry.
Osman has a big enemy now.
Who?
Geyhatu's hunter dog...
the Black Shaman Togay.
Please contact us for any inquiries
turkision@gmail.com